<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet
      title="Run TestCases">
   <intro>
   <description>
     In a few steps, this cheat sheet will guide you through the run and evaluation of TestCases.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         title="Create TestCampaign">
      <description>
        In your <b>TestSpecification</b>, select one or more TestCases. Right-click your mouse.
        You can either choose <b>&quot;RunTest&quot;</b> or <b>&quot;Create TestCampaign&quot;</b>.
        If you choose &quot;RunTest&quot;, a TestCampaign will be created and run directly.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Run TestCampaign">
      <description>
         You can (re-) run your TestCampaign by clicking the <b>&quot;Execute&quot;</b> button.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Generate Report">
      <description>
        You can generate a report of your run by clicking the <b>&quot;Generate Report&quot;</b> button.
        A folder browser will open where you can choose the folder you want the report to be saved in.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="View TestCases and TestSteps">
      <description>
       In the TestCampaignEditor in the column <b>&quot;TestCase/TestStep&quot</b>; the whole TestCampaign structure will be shown as a tree.
       You can double-click with your mouse on the single TestCases or TestSteps, and the TestCase will open in an editor. 
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="View LogFiles">
      <description>
       	In the TestCampaignEditor in the column <b>&quot;TestCase/TestStep&quot</b>; the whole TestCampaign structure will be shown as a tree.
       	You can open a LogFile to an item if you right-click on it with your mouse, then choose <b>&quot;Show LogFile&quot</b>;.
       	If you select the TestCampaign, the log file for it including all testcases and teststeps will open in an editor.
       	If you have selected &quot;Add separate logfile for each testcase&quot; in the GlobalTester Preferences and select a TestCase, 
       	the log file for this TestCase will open.
       	If you have selected &quot;Add separate logfile for each testcase&quot; in the GlobalTester Preferences and select a TestStep,
       	the log file for this TestCase will open with the line number of the beginning of the TestStep highlighted.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Browse TestCampaign Executions">
      <description>
         
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Status of TestCase Execution in TestCampaign Execution">
      <description>
         In the TestCampaignEditor in the column <b>&quot;Status&quot</b>;
         the status of the TestCase execution will be shown. It is either <b>&quot;FAILURE&quot</b>; (red), <b>&quot;WARNING&quot</b>; (yellow), or just green. 
      </description>
   </item>
   

</cheatsheet>
